Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Personal
  - Requests for Information or Action
    - Requests for information/action. 1990. (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Requests for information/action. 1991-1992. (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Scrapbook
    - [Reel tape] Today's Trends--KTRH--2:30 pm, Sunday, July 22. 1956. (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - [Video tape--reel type] Pain segment, "Today Show," 27 February. 1977. (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - "Secret Out" article - photo copy. 1942. (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Personal: Awards and Honors. 1942-1977. (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Conquest of Pain - Sunday Times, London. 1958. (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Notizario Isole Eolie ( and scrapbook clippings). 1957-1982. (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - News article clippings. 1959. (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - JJ Bonica: Living History Videotape. 1970-1979. (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Scrapbook duplicates [need conservation attention]. 1972-1981. (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Dr. B's scrapbook duplicate copies. 1976-1986. (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - "Masked Marvel" article from People. 1977. (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - People. 1977. (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Scrapbook. 1977-1979. (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Personal: Awards & Honors. 1978-1988. (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - "The Pain Killer" by JJB Jr., Northwest magazine. 1978. (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Scrapbook. 1978-1979. (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Press release - WFSA Presidency. 1980. (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Corresp. re: publicity. 1982. (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - Article, New York magazine. 1982. (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - New York magazine. 1982. (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - LA Times article. 1991. (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Photographs-misc. 1992. (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Older photos - Publicity. nd. (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Photo from trip to China. 1983. (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Photographs. nd. (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - Phototgraphs - Dr. B. - current. nd. (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - Photos. nd. (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Misc Photos. nd. (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - Photographs. nd. (Box 71, Folder 57)
    - Photos of Northwestern U. D.S. degree. 1989. (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - Puerto Rico file [photo]. 1973. (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - Negative from article in People. 1981. (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - Photographs. nd. (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - ARC [photos]. nd. (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - [Caricature of JJB by Jorge Seabra in Portugal]. 1971. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Work-Related
    - Personal: Future professional activities. 1971-1978. (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Dr. B's personal equiptment. 1972. (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Personal: Confidential Memoranda - Faculty eval. 1972. (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Personal: UW summary of outside Professional activities. 1972-1987. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 220 Forms, Dr. B. 1973. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Personal: Requests for sabbatical leave. 1973,1984. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Personal: Committee Appointments. 1974. (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Personal: Clinical services. 1974. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Personal: Departmental Budget. 1977. (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Faculty activities for deaprtmental annual report. 1977-1986. (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Personal: continuing Ed. Credits. 1977-1987. (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Letter to former & present faculty, staff, residents on resignation of dept. chair. 1978. (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Dr. B's leave requests. 1978-1987. (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Bonica's monthly calendar. 1979-1980. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Annual Faculty report. 1979-1980. (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - JJB lectureship, New York - Eastern Pain Assoc. 1979-1981. (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - JJ.B Lectureship, SEattle. 1979-1983. (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Clinical activities: corresp. 1979-1985. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - UW-related Personal affairs (parking, phone, ins, etc.). 1979-1993. (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Clinical Conferences. 1981. (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Dr. B's monthly cal. 1981-1982. (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Corresp. re: clinical commitment. 1981-1984. (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Individual activity report - Dr. B. 1981-1984. (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Corresp. w/Dr. Hornbein & Jean Chapman re: Dr. B's leave. 1981-1987. (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - John J. Emma Bonica Fellowship - Tauber Institute. 1982-. (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Clinical Activities: corresp. re pts. 1982-1983. (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - JJB scholastic award Tacoma,. 1983. (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - School of Medicine: Faculty Effort Analysis Survey. 1983. (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Dept. of Anesthesiology Alumni mailing list. 1984. (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Mailing lists. 1985. (Box 71, Folder 30)
  - Writing/Consulting
    - Correspondence re: writing invitations/commitments. 1971-1975. (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Writing/Speaking Schedules. 1975-1977. (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Jessica Brown, St. Louis post Dispatch Interview. 1977. (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - Pheochromocytoma Study - E.I. Eger (Ed Pavlin - UW coordinator). 1977. (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - The Medical Letter - Acupuncture. 1977. (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - Manuscript Review Requests & Replies. 1977-1980. (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - C.G. Edizioni Medico Scientifiche C. Ciocatto. 1979. (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - The Fielding Inst. Review: Reid Wilson's proposal. 1979. (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - Writing - Speaking Commitments. 1979-1980. (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - Evaluation of Dept. U. Mass. 1980. (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - Dealing with Pain, Amer. Cancer Soc. Reviewed by Dr. B. 1980. (Box 69, Folder 51)
    - MSS Review - Journal Behav. Med. 1981. (Box 69, Folder 52)
    - International Advisory Board, course on Pharmacological Basis of Anesthesiology. 1982. (Box 69, Folder 53)
    - Cancer Info Service (A Program of FHCRC). 1981. (Box 69, Folder 54)
    - Review of speech by Dr. Rosomoff for Board of Industrial Insurance Appeals. 1981. (Box 69, Folder 55)
    - Reviews. 1981-. (Box 69, Folder 56)
    - Questionaires. 1981-. (Box 69, Folder 57)
    - Reviews, J.A.M.A. 1981-. (Box 69, Folder 58)
    - American Journal of Psychiatry. 1981-. (Box 69, Folder 59)
    - Review of script systemic toxic.Breon. 1981. (Box 69, Folder 60)
    - Research Survey - Pain Center. 1981-1982. (Box 69, Folder 61)
    - Review of grant application for NCI by Dr. B. 1982. (Box 69, Folder 62)
    - Review of booklet on pain for Am. Cancer Soc. 1983. (Box 69, Folder 63)
    - Review of Honors Papers. 1983. (Box 69, Folder 64)
    - Travel/writing deadlines. 1988. (Box 69, Folder 65)
    - Writing. 1988-1992. (Box 69, Folder 66)
- Publications
  - Management of Pain, 1st edition
    - Outlines. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Preface and introduction. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 1: The Anatomical Basis of Pain. Final draft. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 1: The Anatomical Basis of Pain. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 2: Neurophysiological Basis of Pain. Rough and 2nd copy. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Chapter 2: Neurophysiological Basis of Pain. Final draft. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 3: Physiopathologic Basis of Pain. Rough notes. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 3: The Physiopathologic Basis of Pain. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Chapter 3: The Physiopathologic Basis of Pain. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Chapter 3: The Physiopathologic Basis of Pain. Final copy. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Chapter 4: The Psychologic Basis of Pain. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Chapter 5: The Mental and Physical Effects of Pain. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Chapter 6: History and General Principles of the Management of Pain with Analgesic Block. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Chapter 6: History and General Principles of the Management of Pain with Analgesic Block. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Chapter 7: Fundamental Considerations. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Chapter 7: Fundamental Considerations. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Chapter 8: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Cranial nerves. (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Cervical Somatic Nerves. (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Brachial Blocks. (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Brachial Block. (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Articles. (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Brachial Plexus Block. (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Brachial Plexus Block. (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Thoracic Somatic Nerves. (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Lumbar Somatic Nerves. (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Sacral and Coccygeal. Rough. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 9: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Blocking the Somatic Spinal Nerves. Sacral and Coccygeal Nerves. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 10: Technic of Nerve Blocking-The Autonomic Nervous System. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Chapter 11: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Subarachnoid Block. Draft. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Chapter 11: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Subarachnoid Block. Articles. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Chapter 12: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Peridural Block. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 12: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Peridural Block. Data re: clinical evaluation of spinal peridural. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 13: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Local Block. Rough. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Chapter 13: Technic of Nerve Blocking-Local Block. Local Surface Anesthetic Agents. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Chapter 14: Technic of Nerve Blocking-The Intravenous Administration of Local Anesthetic Agents in the Management of Pain. Final. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Chapter 15: The Use of Opiates and Other Analgesics in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Chapter 15: The Use of Opiates and Other Analgesics in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Chapter 16: Psychotherapeutic Methods in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Chapter 16: Psychotherapeutic Methods in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Chapter 17: Physical Therapeutic Methods in the Management of Pain. Final. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Chapter 18: Orthopedic Methods in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Chapter 18: Orthopedic Methods in the Management of Pain. Final copy. (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Chapter 19: Roentgen Therapy in the Management of Pain. (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Chapter 20: Neurosurgical Methods in the Management of Pain. Final copy. (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Original outline. 1950. (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Lea & Febiger [correspondence]. 1950-1957. (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Rough sketches, nd. (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Polis, Miss Joy. [Correspondence,] 1950-1952. (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Coleman, Miss Virginia. [Correspondence,] 1951-1953. (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - References, nd. (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Page proof, chapters 6 & 28. (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Letters about, 1953-1955. (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Publicity, 1953. (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Reviews, 1953. (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Book reviews, 1954. (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Reviews, 1954-1963. (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Sales of, 1954-1957. (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Corrections, 1957-1958. (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Translation, 1957-1959. (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with publisher, 1962. (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Sale of reprint, 1978-1981. (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Requests to purchase, 1978-1990. (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Negatives. (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Proofs, figures 1 - 228. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Matted illustrations. (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Management of Pain, 2nd edition
    - Ahles. Chapter 83. Pageproof. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Almquist. Chapter 51. Upper Extremity Pain 2/74. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. 1st Draft 1/86. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. 1st Draft copyedited by Bonica 6/86. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. Revised 1st Draft 10/86. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. Revisted 1st Draft-copyedited. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. 1987. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. 2nd Draft. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. 2nd Draft ed. by Bonica 1988. (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Almquist, Edward E. Chapter 51. Pageproofs 1989. (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Anderson. [No chapter number]. 1972-1973. (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Ansell/Gee 1972-1976. (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Kidney-Ureter-62 1st Draft 8/85 & prev. corresp. (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. 11/85 Revision. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Kidney & Ureter 62 12/85. (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Kidney & Ureter 1986. (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Kidney & Ureter 11/87 orig. (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 62. Kidney -62 Pageproofs. (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic Pain 6/85. (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic Pain 11/85. (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic Pain 2/86. (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic Pain 10-12/86. (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic & Perineal Pain Final Draft. (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - Ansell, Julian S. Chapter 68. Pelvic & Perineal Pain Marked Proofs. (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis 1st Draft 83-85. (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis 1985 Revision. (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis 1987 Revisions. (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis Final Editing 1-2/88. (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis Copyedited Galleys 5/89. (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Barber, Joseph. Chapter 84. Hypnosis Pageproofs 1&2. (Box 79, Folder 30)
    - Bell. [No chapter number]. Masticatory Pain 1972-1973. (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Benedetti, Costantino. Part V, Section A, Introduction. Draft & ... (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Benedetti, Costantino. Chapter 78. Systemic Analgesics 1988. (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Benedetti, Costantino. Chapter 78. System Analgesics Revised. (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Benedetti, Costantino. Chapter 78. System Analgesics Pageproofs 1989. (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Benson. [No chapter number]. Gynecologic Pain 1974-75. (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Berges. [No chapter number]. 1972. (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. Radiation Therapy 89. (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. Radiation Therapy draft 2. (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. Radiation Therapy draft 3. (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. HOME OFFICE: Rad. Thpy. 89 copy ed. (Box 79, Folder 41)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. Radiation Therapy draft 3 copy ed. (Box 79, Folder 42)
    - Berry, Roger. Chapter 89. Radiation Therapy Pageproofs. (Box 79, Folder 43)
    - Bigos. [No chapter number]. Low Back Pain 1st draft & corresp. 1984-1986. (Box 79, Folder 44)
    - Bigos. [No chapter number]. Low Back Pain Revisions 2/87-4/87. (Box 79, Folder 45)
    - Bigos. [No chapter number]. Los Back Pain 9/87. (Box 79, Folder 46)
    - Bigos. [No chapter number]. Low Back Pain 2/88. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Bigos. [No chapter number]. Low Back Pain 1988 revision. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Black. [No chapter number]. 1972-1974. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback Corresp. & 1st draft. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback Rev & corresp. 84-87. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback Publisher copy 9-87. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback 8/87 revision. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback 2/88 Edit by Bonica. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback -83 1st pageproof 5/89. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback -83 2nd pageproof 7/89. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Blanchard, Edward B. Chapter 83. Biofeedback final pageproof 11/89. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Bond. [No chapter number]. 1983-1985. (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Bonica, John J. Part I, Introduction. Frontmatter 1989 4/89. (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Bonica, John J. Part I, Introduction. Frontmatter copyedited 5/89. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Bonica, John J. Part I, Introduction. Frontmatter Revised 6/89. (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Bonica, John J. Part I, Introduction. Frontmatter Pageproofs 7/89. (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Bonica, John J. Part I, Introduction. 87-88. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Intro 1984 drafts. (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Introduction Draft 2 85-86. (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Intro. Draft 3 1/87. (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Intro Draft 3 copyedited. (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Intro Obsolete. (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 1. Intro Pageproofs 1988. (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 2. Draft 1. (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 2. Draft 2. (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 2. Pageproofs. (Box 80, Folder 26)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3&4. Corresp. & comments. (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3&4. Reviewed by Casey 1986. (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3&4. Reviewd by Dubner 1986. (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Figures and Legends 1987. (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. 1st draft 1986. (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 1 copyedited. (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 2 2-3/86. (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 2 copyedited. (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 3 4/86. (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 4 5/86. (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 5 6-7/86. (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 6 9/86. (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 6 revised 10/86. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 7 12/86. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 8 1/87. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 9 1/87. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 9-R 2/87. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 10 3/87. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Draft 10-R 9/87. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Layout 5/88. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. First Marked Proofs 5/88. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Revisions 7/88. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. 2nd marked proofs 9/88. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. 3rd proofs 3/89. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Illustrations. (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 2 3/86. (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 3 5/86. (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 4 5/86. (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 5 7/86. (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 5 Reviewed by Casey 7/86. (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 5 Reviewed by Chapman 8/86. (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 6 9/86. (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 7 12/86. (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 8 1/87. (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 8 edited 1/87. (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 9 7/87. (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 9 copyedited 9/87. (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Draft 9 copyedited w/JJB's. (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Final Revisions & Proofs 11/88. (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 4. Reference articles. (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 1 3/86. (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 2 5/86. (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 3 6/86. (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 4 7/86. (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 5 9/86. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 6 12/86. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 6 copyedited 12/86. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 7 3/87. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Draft 7 copyedited 9/87. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. illustrations (Draft). (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Pageproof 4/88. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Pageproofs 6/88. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 6. Pageproof 2/89. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 7. Draft 1 4/86. (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 7. Draft 2 5/86. (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 7. Draft 3 6/86. (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 7. Draft 4 7/86. (Box 82, Folder 13)